（フー）チャクラを持たない
植物のような分身の→
It appears to be a jutsu
where a seed-like clone
小さなもとが
チャクラを持つ生命体に寄生して→
parasitizes a life form with chakra
and feeds on its host's chakra.
宿主のチャクラを
吸い取る術のようです。
（トルネ）だから　お前でも
気づかなかったのか。
So that's why you didn't notice it.
（フー）おそらく　会談場での
暁の忍術だろう。
Most likely a ninjutsu of the Akatsuki
we saw at the meeting.
（トルネ）で　どうだ？　もう１人
ずっと　つけてるやつのほうは。
And what about the other one
who has been following us all along?
（フー）そいつは　今も
俺たちを尾行している。
He continues to tail us.
Probably the Byakugan user
from the Hidden Mist.
おそらくは　霧の白眼。
（ダンゾウ）やつか…。
Him?
There.
（青）よし。
これにかかれば儲けものだが…。
It would be a stroke of luck
if he falls for this.
（トルネ）お前のトラップは特別だ。
うまくいく。
Your traps are special.
It'll work.
生死は問わんが　右目は
必ず　えぐり取っておけ。
Dead or alive, make sure
you gouge out his right eye.
はっ！
Yes, sir!
（鬼鮫）干柿鬼鮫。
以後　お見知りおきを。
Kisame Hoshigaki,
pleased to meet you after the fact.
（キラービー）干柿鬼鮫と。
Kisame Hoshigaki, eh?
Ink in your mouth…
口から墨とは　やはり
噂どおりの　タコ野郎でしたね。
The rumors are true.
You really are an octopus brat.
♪ 「さめざめと泣かせてやるぜ
この鮫ヤロー」
I’m gonna make you weep!
You sharky creep!
ウィ～！！
《キン：尾獣の衣　チャクラの尾が七本！
A Tailed Beast Cloak with
only seven chakra tails…
ビーは
本気ってことにならないかい》
Does this mean
you're going to get serious?
知ってるか？
何をですか？
Did you know?
Know what?
Octopi eat sharks!
タコは　サメを食うんだよ！
刀がかわした！
The sword dodged on its own!
ふん！
ビー！
Bee!
《また　チャクラを吸い取って
更に　やつの刀がでかくなったよ》
That sword sucked out
Bee's chakra again
and has grown even bigger!
今回は　サメが　タコを食うようですね。
This time, the shark shall
devour the octopus.
《あの鮫肌とかいう刀
大食いで早食いだが→
That sword Samehada's got
a big appetite and it's a speed-eater,
一度に食えるチャクラの量は
尾が六本分ね…》
but it looks like it can only devour
six tails' worth of chakra at one time.
《このバージョンで　これなら…。
If that's the situation with this version,
次のバージョンでいけるか》
then my next version
should do the trick.
鮫肌が
ここまで大きくなったのは→
Samehada has never grown
this big before.
初めてですよ。
喜び方もハンパじゃありませんね。
Its delight is not trivial either.
どうするんだい？　ビー。
What'll we do, Bee?
（八尾）俺も出る。　尾獣化しろ！
I'll help. Enter Tailed Beast State!
（メイ）マーキングの流れからして
青は　こっちのようですね。
Judging from the markings,
Ao went this way.
先を急ぎましょう。
（長十郎）はい！
Let us hurry.
Yes, ma'am!
Tailed Beast vs.
The Tailless Tailed Beast
Take care of my body, Torune.
そろそろ　俺の体を頼む。　トルネ。
A booby trap. It must be Danzo's.
ブービートラップ…。　ダンゾウだな！
CURSE
《青：むぅ…
なぜ　俺の体が見える？》
Why am I seeing
my own body?!
（フー）かかったな。
Gotcha.
What's going on?
《青：どういうことだ？》
You are under my Mind Transfer
Puppet Curse Jutsu.
（フー）心転傀儡呪印の術。
《しまった！
攻撃した者を呪う→
Damn it! Was this
a curse-type Mind Transfer Jutsu
that activates itself when
the object is attacked?!
呪印型の心転身の術か！》
Your mind is now sealed inside
that puppet.
（フー）お前の意識は　今
その人形の中に封じている。
そして　お前の体は→
And I am in possession…
この俺が　のっとっている。
of your body.
クソ…　やはり駄目か…。
Damn it. It's useless.
Forget it.
《やめておけ。
それは　俺たち霧の暗部→
That is a Barrier Ninjutsu that
only us Hidden Mist Black Ops,
追い忍部隊でしか解けない
結界忍術だ。
the Shinobi Tracking Unit, can undo.
霧が　唯一保有する
貴重な白眼…。
My Byakugan is precious,
the only one that the Mist possesses.
簡単には　取り返せると思うな》
Do not think that you'll be able
to reclaim it easily.
眼に危機が迫ると
自動的に発動するってやつか…。
So it self-activates
when the eye is at risk, eh?
通称　死体処理班のお前らが→
A fitting jutsu coming from you guys,
also known as the Undertaker Squad.
考えそうな術だ。
簡単とは思っていない。
I don't expect it to be easy.
お前の眼をえぐれば→
Taking your eye means that I,
as the jutsu caster, will lose my own eye.
術者本体の俺の眼も潰れる…。
わかってるだろ。
You know that.
《ダンゾウの命令か…。
部下を　なんだと思ってる》
So it's Danzo's orders?
Just what does he think of
his subordinates?
（フー）この俺の眼ひとつで→
If the Mist's military power becomes
greatly diminished because of it,
霧の戦力が大きく低下するなら
安いものだ。
losing one of my eyes is
a cheap price to pay.
結界のせいで
今のままでは無理だがな。
Though, thanks to your barrier,
it's not going to happen at this rate.
But there are plenty of other options.
だが　やりようなら
いくらでもある。
Enter Tailed Beast State, Bee!
《尾獣化しろ　ビー！》
No way, fool, ya fool!
《駄目だ　バカ野郎！　コノ野郎！
An attack with you would
be way too huge
八っつあんとじゃ
一撃がでかすぎて→
and would destroy the area.
辺りが　むちゃくちゃになる。
今は　キンちゃん師匠も
ポン太もいるんだぜ。
Master Kin and Ponta are
here with us, don't forget!
そのうえ
せっかく　身を隠したのに→
Besides, I finally managed to
sneak off under the radar.
お前を出したら　ここに→
If I let you out, it'll be like
announcing that Killer Bee is here!
キラービーがいるんだよ！
ってことに　なるだろ！》
《グダグダと　お前らしくねえな　ビー！
It's not like you to make excuses, Bee!
So what'll you do?
Fight in Version 2 State?
なら　どうすんだ？
バージョン２でやんのかよ？》
《オーイエー！　ただし
さっきからのやり取りで→
Oh yeah.
‘Cept most of my chakra got taken away
during those last few exchanges,
俺のチャクラは　ほとんど
持ってかれちまった。
so lend me yours.
お前のチャクラ　貸してくれ》
《けっ！　俺がいなけりゃ→
If it weren't for me,
you'd have lost a long time ago.
とっくに
敗者になってるとこだぜ》
Ya sure got a cheeky personality,
生意気な口上！
but I'm still grateful for
your hospitality, yeah!
そのご厚情に感謝する。　イエ～！
Huh?
Going into a Tailed Beast State, eh?
尾獣化ですか？
いや　これは尾獣の力を
人型に抑え込んだ→
No, this is a Tailed Beast's power
trapped in a humanoid form.
バージョン２！
It's Version 2 State!
（キラービー）ラリアット！
Lariat!
《鮫肌が
トリップするほど騒いでいる。
Samehada is so excited
it's tripping out.
さっきとは比べものにならない
チャクラの量　質…。
The chakra earlier is nothing compared
to this volume and quality.
これだけのチャクラを
正気を保ったまま→
I'm amazed he can control this
much chakra without losing his mind.
コントロールするとは…》
There's no way to devour
this much chakra.
《これほどの量
食いきれませんね》
（キラービー）ウィ～！
やったよ！
You did it!
バージョン１まで戻されるとは…。
I can't believe I was reduced back
to Version 1 State.
生きとるよ！
さっさと　とどめだよ！
He's still alive! Hurry and finish him!
やって…　くれましたね…。
You've sure done it.
なんなの！？
What is that?!
私は　相手が
強ければ強いほど→
The stronger my opponent,
the stronger I become.
それに比例して　強くなる。
疲れることも…。
I do not tire.
倒れることもない。
I do not fall.
敵対する者のチャクラを奪い→
So his blade steals his enemy's chakra
それを持ち主に
スタミナとして渡す仕組みか！？
and transfers it to its master
in the form of stamina?
だから　尾を持たない尾獣などと
呼ばれていましてね。
And that's why
I'm called the Tailless Tailed Beast.
《水遁！　大爆水衝波！》
Water Style:
Super Exploding Water Shock Wave!
何をする気だ？
What do you plan to do?
I'm simply going to jump down
and behead you.
このまま飛び降りて
この首を切断する。
眼が無理なら　首ごと
木ノ葉に持っていくしかあるまい。
If I can't remove your eye,
then I'll just have to take
your entire head back to the Leaf with me.
死ぬ気か？
You're going to kill yourself?
いや　首を切る寸前に
この心転身の術を解く。
No. I'll undo this Mind Transfer Jutsu
just before the blade cuts your neck.
とにかく　お前は死に
自分の体に戻った俺は→
Either way, you'll die.
And I, back in my body, can retrace
my steps here to grab your head.
後で　ここへ引き返し→
お前の首を
持っていくというわけだ。
まぁいい。
そういうことなら用心しろよ。
Fine. Just make sure you're careful.
Or else you'll fail.
でなけりゃ　失敗するぞ。
どういうことだ！？
What do you mean?
ビビって　少しでも早く
その術を解いたら→
Because if you get nervous and
release that jutsu an instant too soon,
俺は必ず　鎌を防ぐ！
I'll defend myself from your sickle!
If I'm not dead,
もし　俺が死んでなかったら→
the tables will be turned
when you come to get my head.
お前が　ここに首を取りにきたとき
立場が逆転すると思え。
Remember that.
ハァハァ…。
助かりました。
何があったの？
Saved.
What happened?
敵の術にかかり
体の自由がきかなくて。
I was caught in the enemy's jutsu
and couldn't move my body.
助けがなければ　死んでいました。
If you hadn't come, I would be dead.
That was a very close call.
いや
危ないところでしたよ　本当に。
心配をかけて　すまない。
I'm sorry I made you worry.
自由がきかない…。
幻術か何かの類ね。
Couldn't move?
It must have been a genjutsu
or something.
心転身の術の系統です。
It was a type of Mind Transfer Jutsu.
その右目
やつらは白眼を狙ったようね。
Your right eye…
The enemy was after the Byakugan,
weren't they?
危うく潰されるところでした。
They almost succeeded in smashing it.
すみません。　この手の縄を→
I'm sorry, but can you untie me?
解いてもらえませんか？
ええ。
Of course.
その右目の術も
私が解いてあげますよ。
I'll also undo that jutsu protecting
your right eye.
すみません　助かります。
Thank you, that will help.
なんだろう　あれ…。
What is that?
駄目だ！
No!
He hasn't undone
the Mind Transfer Jutsu yet!
《そいつは　まだ
心転身の術を解いてはいない！》
《うまくいった。　水影が
右目の術を解けるなら好都合。
She fell for it.
If the Mizukage can undo the jutsu
protecting this right eye,
I couldn't ask for anything better.
白眼を潰して
すぐに心転身を解ける》
I can destroy the Byakugan and
then undo the Mind Transfer Jutsu.
《こいつ　感知タイプだったやつか！
He must be that Sensory-Type ninja!
This was his plan all along!
はなから
これを狙ってやがったな！
駄目です　水影様！》
No, Lady Mizukage!
これでよし。
This should do.
水影様…。
Lady Mizukage?
ヒラメカレイを貸して　長十郎。
Lend me your Hiramekarei, Chojuro.
はぁ？
Huh?
あなたは青じゃない。
You are not Ao.
私は　その右目の術を
解くことはできません。
I cannot undo the jutsu
on that right eye.
このことは青もよく知っています。
Ao knows that well.
それに青は　長十郎に
謝ったりはしません。　絶対に。
Besides, Ao would never apologize
to Chojuro.
カマをかけたか。
You played me…
you sly old vixen—
食えないババア…　イテェ！
Ow!
I-I wasn't the one who said that…ma'am.
私が言ったんでは
ないんですが…。
Oh, you're back to normal.
あら　元に戻ったのね。
殺す…　木ノ葉の感知タイプ！
I'll kill him!
That Sensory-Type Hidden Leaf ninja!
ヒラメカレイのほうじゃなくて
よかったですね　先輩。
It's a good thing she didn't use
the Hiramekarei on you, sir.
フー。
どうだ？
Foo.
Well?
すみません。　失敗に終わりました。
Forgive me, sir. I have failed.
仕方あるまい。
It cannot be helped.
The longer this battle drags on,
（鬼鮫）戦いが長引けば長引くほど
あなたたちは→
the more chakra will be shaved from you
and the greater you will weaken.
削り取られ　弱っていく。
And I'll grow proportionately stronger.
が　私は削り取った分
どんどん強くなっていく。
ビー！　やつの刀を奪うしかないよ！
Bee! You must take his sword away!
あの刀が
やつの強さのカギになってるよ！
That sword is the key to his strength!
私の体から
引き剥がせれば　ですがね。
That's if you can pull it off my body.
He merged with his sword?!
刀と融合した！？
He's like a fish that became a man.
《まるで　人間のようになった魚？
Or is it a man that's half fish?
いや　半分だけ
魚になった人間？》
That's too much explaining!
He's half fish, half man!
《キン：説明が長いよ！
半漁人だよ！》
Here I come!
では　いきますよ！
At this rate,
both Master Kin and Ponta will drown.
《キラービー：このままじゃ
キンちゃん師匠も　ポン太も…。
First, we have to get out of the water!
水から脱出するのが先だぜ。
ヨウ！》
（鬼鮫）この水遁からは
逃げられないですよ。
You cannot escape this Water Style Jutsu.
今の私と　あなたたちでは
地の利が違いすぎますからね。
I have the advantage in
this location right now.
I can't see the boundary!
So much water! So crazy!
《先が見えねえ。　どんだけ～》
Bee! Behind you!
《キン：ビー　後ろ！》
《この状況！　上等！
負けるかよ！》
These circumstances are hunky-dory!
I won't be taken down, sorry!
This isn't the time for
your lame rapping!
《八尾：うぜぇ　ラップ
かましてる場合か。
The water bubble is in motion
あの半漁人を中心にして→
and that half-fish guy
is at the center!
この水も一緒に
移動してやがるんだよ。　気づけ！
Pay attention!
それに　やつのほうが
水中では速い。
And he's faster under water
than we are!
しかも　半漁人ってぐらいだから
たぶん　エラ呼吸だ。
Plus he's half fish,
so he probably breathes through gills!
ただ逃げても
いずれ　やられるぜ》
Just running away
is gonna get us killed.
So what'll we do?
《なら　どうする？》
《暁のターゲットは　お前だ。　ビー。
Akatsuki's target is you, Bee!
Leave that enka geezer
and the raccoon
その演歌じじいと
たぬきは置いて→
２人とは　違う方向へ逃げろ。
and run in a different direction!
He's definitely gonna come after you.
やつは　必ずお前を追う》
I see. That way, those two can…
《キラービー：なるほど。
そうすりゃ　２人は》
Right! While he's pursuing you,
the water will move with him.
《八尾：おう。　やつが
お前を追っているうちに→
水も　やつを中心に
移動していき→
Then those two can
get out of the water.
いずれは
水から　２人は出る》
All right! Now come this way!
《よし　こっちへついてこい》
What?!
《なにっ！？》
八尾は生け捕りがルールですが→
I must capture the Eight-Tails alive,
こいつらの生死は
関係ありませんからね。
but there's no rule against
killing these two!
《させないヨウ　バカ野郎！》
I ain't letting that happen, ya fool!
Wha—?!
I got you!
かかりましたね！
Suction pads?!
吸盤！？
《捕まえたぜ！
Gotcha!
No way will you keep
taking my chakra.
そう何度も
タダでは　チャクラやんねえよ！
バカ野郎　この野郎！》
Fool, ya fool!
You really are worthy of being
called the perfect Jinchuriki.
完璧な人柱力と
呼ばれただけはありますね。
To be able to change just one part of
yourself into your Tailed Beast is impressive.
このサイズで
一部だけを尾獣化するとは。
All right, they're out.
《よし　出たぞ！》
You seem to be
having trouble breathing.
ずいぶんと苦しそうですね。
いいアイデアでしたが
私の体に触れている以上→
It was a good idea,
but as long as you're touching me,
you'll continue losing chakra.
チャクラは　どんどん
なくなっていきますよ。
I can see why Samehada
can't contain his excitement.
《鮫肌が喜び　震えるのがわかる。
He has discovered
his favorite kind of chakra.
大好物のチャクラを
見つけてしまったようですね。
暁で私ほど　生け捕りの
上手い者はいなくてねぇ。
No one in the Akatsuki is as good as
I am at taking prey alive.
この水牢　鮫踊りの術。
This Water Prison Shark Dance Jutsu
is so much fun
生存できるギリギリまで
チャクラを削る加減を→
because I can probe
the amount of chakra to shave
until you're just on the verge of death.
見極めるのが
おもしろいんですよ》
まぁ　たまに
失敗することもありますがね。
I must admit to failing once in a while.
《こうなったら　また　ラリアットだ。
I guess I have to use Lariat again.
I just have to time it right.
うまく　タイミングをあわせて…》
Don't!
《よせ！　水中で
こいつには勝てねえよ！
You can't beat him underwater!
さっきのタコ足のやつで
更に警戒もしてやがる。
That last attempt with
the octopus leg put him on guard.
ここは　いったん逃げろ！
Just make a run for it!
Use that!
あれを使え！》
ん？
Ink… A smokescreen.
《これは墨！？　目くらまし…。
You are an octopus, after all.
やっぱり　タコ野郎ですね。
が！》
However…
With my body merged with Samehada,
I can detect chakra through my skin.
この鮫肌と融合した
私の体は→
チャクラを肌で感じとる。
チャクラも
そろそろ　底をつきそうですね！
It seems you'll run
out of chakra soon.
ハァハァ…　ビー！
Bee…
今　行くよ。　ビー！
I'm coming…Bee!
八尾も　あっけなかったですね。
The Eight-Tails turned out to
be rather disappointing too.
また　チョロチョロされて尾獣化されても
厄介ですからね。
I can't chance you squirming around
and going into
a Tailed Beast State again.
念のために
足を切っておきますか。
So I'm going to cut off your legs
as a precaution.
ハァハァ…。
《八尾：俺のチャクラも
ほとんど持っていきやがって…。
He took most of my chakra too!
くそっ　ビー　起きろ！
Damn it! Get up, Bee!
マジで　やべえぞ！》
We're in a real bind!
きれいに
スパッとは切れませんがね！
Though, my blade doesn't cut cleanly!
どうしたんですか！？
What's the matter?
くっ！
まさか　八尾に懐くとは…。
Don't tell me you've become
attached to the Eight-Tails.
そんなに　そいつのチャクラが
気に入りましたか　鮫肌！
うっ…　うぅ…。
私から奪ったチャクラを！
ちょうどいい。
お互い　武器を交換といきますか。
ふむ…　この刀。
きれいに　スパッと切れそうですね。
ここだ！
《エンピツ！？》
惜しかったな…。
確かに　惜しかったですね。
これを狙ってたんですね。
（シー）ビー　遅くなって　すまない。
ブラザー。
雷影…　なぜ　ここが？
（シー）あれだけでかい水の塊なら
視覚で　わかる。
その中に　八尾とビーのチャクラが
混ざっていることが感知できた。
（ダルイ）むやみやたらに
他人のチャクラを吸い取って→
利用するんだもんよ。
バレバレだっつうのよ。
やっぱ　バレちまったな。
鮫肌のやつ　更に　チャクラを八尾に！
やるぞ！
オーケー　ブラザー。
水遁！　大鮫弾！
（２人）ダブルラリアット！
さすがに速すぎますね…。
フッ。
ブラザー。
ノォ～！！
１人で　チョロチョロしおって～！
利き腕じゃなくても　き…　効く！
危機だヨウ！